whiskeyriff.com 2017-12-03

# Privacy | Whiskey Riff

_Policy Effective Date: December 21 st 2016_

Welcome to Whiskey Riff (“Whiskey Riff,” “we,” or “us”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers the website [ **www.whiskeyriff.com**](http://www.whiskeyriff.com/) (the “Whiskey Riff Site”) belonging to Momentum Media, LLC.

The Whiskey Riff Site is a website for users to enjoy the content posted by Whiskey Riff and other users.  The content, our video player, and any other features, tools, materials, or other services offered in connection with the Whiskey Riff Site from time to time by Whiskey Riff on any device or platform are referred to collectively as the “Whiskey Riff.”

The Policy describes:

  * The information we collect and how we collect it;
  * What we do with the information we collect;
  * Information sharing and disclosure;
  * How you can access and update your information;
  * How we protect information;
  * Linked sites and advertisements;
  * Users from outside the United States;
  * Children;
  * How to contact us;
  * Your California privacy rights;
  * No rights of third parties; and
  * Changes to this policy.

**The Information We Collect and How We Collect It**

How we collect and store information depends on the Whiskey Riff Services you use and the devices you use to access the Whiskey Riff Services. You can use some of the Whiskey Riff Services without providing any information other than that automatically collected as described below.

We may collect information about you during your use of the Whiskey Riff Services, including your name, username, password, email address, and information you provide or post on the Whiskey Riff Services or allow us to access when you do certain things, such as:

  * Enter registration information for the Whiskey Riff Services;
  * Enter a sweepstakes or contest or register for a promotion;
  * Participate in voting or polling activities;
  * Request certain features (e.g., newsletters);
  * Sign up to receive SMS (text message) notifications;
  * Download or use one of our mobile applications;
  * Connect with the Whiskey Riff Services or otherwise allow us to access certain information about you via Facebook and other social networking services (collectively, “social networking services”); or
  * Post content to or on the Whiskey Riff Services.

We may collect and store your user ID associated with the social networking site account that you use to sign in to your Whiskey Riff account or connect or use with the Whiskey Riff Services. When you sign in to your Whiskey Riff account or mobile application with your social networking site account information or otherwise connect to your social networking site account with the Whiskey Riff Services, you authorize Whiskey Riff to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information available to Whiskey Riff through the social networking site interface, including any information that you have made public in connection with your social networking site account, information that the social networking site shares with us, or information that is disclosed as being shared during the sign-in process.

We may also combine information that we collect from you with information we obtain about you from third parties and information derived from any other service we provide.

Please be careful whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose information through the Whiskey Riff Services, such as via social networking sites or in comments you post, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge.

**Cookies and Other Electronic Technologies**

When you use the Whiskey Riff Services, we use persistent and session cookies and other tracking technologies to: (a) store your username and password; (b) analyze the usage of the Whiskey Riff Services; (c) customize the Whiskey Riff Services to your preferences; and (d) control the advertising displayed by the Whiskey Riff Services. We may also use other Internet technologies, such as Flash technologies, Web beacons or pixel tags, and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of the Whiskey Riff Services (including serving you ads when you are on other websites or the Internet when we can access those cookies). We also may include Web beacons in e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether the message has been opened. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather additional information through other methods.

We use these automated technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information we consider to be non-personal information, including: (a) information related to the devices you use to access or interact with our services, such as: IP addresses, geolocation information (as described further below), unique device identifiers and other information about your mobile phone or other mobile device(s), browser types, browser language; and (b) information related to the ways in which you interact with the Whiskey Riff Services, such as: referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time you used the Whiskey Riff Services, and other similar information. We may also capture other data, such as search criteria and results. In some cases, we will associate this information with a unique Whiskey Riff identifier (that cannot be used by it to identify you) for our internal use, in which case your Whiskey Riff identifier will be considered Whiskey Riff information and nothing in this Privacy Policy restricts how Whiskey Riff may use this information.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies by visiting the Help portion of your browser’s toolbar. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in, customize, or use some of the interactive features of the Whiskey Riff Services. Flash cookies operate differently than browser cookies, and cookie management tools available in a web browser will not remove flash cookies. To learn more about how to manage flash cookies, you can visit the [ **Adobe website**](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html) and make changes at the [ **Global Privacy Settings Panel.**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.html)

**Third Party Advertising and Your Choices**

Third parties whose products or services are accessible or advertised via the Whiskey Riff Services may also place cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer, mobile phone, or other device to collect non-personal information about your use of the Whiskey Riff Services. We also allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks and ad servers) to serve tailored ads to you on the Whiskey Riff Services, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer, mobile phone, or other device you use to access the Whiskey Riff Services. We neither have access to, nor does this Policy govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed on your computer, mobile phone, or other device you use to access the Whiskey Riff Services by non-affiliated, third-party ad technology, ad servers, ad networks or any other non-affiliated third parties. Those parties that use these technologies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting as described below. You may receive tailored advertising on your computer through a web browser. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you control cookies from being put on your computer to deliver tailored advertising, you may visit the [ **Network Advertising Initiative’s website**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and/or the [ **Digital Advertising Alliance’s website**](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You also can control advertising cookies from Google, by using its [ **Ads Preference Manager**](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?sig=ACi0TChRwpbntAMM2njihdXfozJJeFxAHpjCee18n5ZUFrx0f8Ag81ZmI54vN5AJDgezZbJiXkYJzMoIPZZ5IrzDPFotiE02HNJqcwNz6mqlWRRkiULVCbvp_56vm0MKiu_uNlIoIfHLZNZk4nM3PMRYKe24CwR6JlanqGrd1kJrWrKSpv82qlzOgEH_yTJ2vTcw2LO912QV&hl=e). Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Whiskey Riff Services, you may still receive advertisements even if you opt-out of tailored advertising.

**Device Location Information**

We may collect different types of information about your location, including general information (e.g., IP address, zip code) and more specific information (e.g., GPS-based functionality on mobile devices used to access the Whiskey Riff  Services), and may use that information to customize the Whiskey Riff  Services with location-based information, advertising, and features. For example, if you provide a zip code that indicates that you live in Chicago, the Whiskey Riff Services may be customized with Chicago-specific information and advertisements. In order to do this, your location information may be passed along to our affiliates, agents, vendors or advertisers. If you access the Whiskey Riff Services through a mobile device and you do not want your device to provide us with location-tracking information, you can disable the GPS or other location-tracking functions on your device, provided your device allows you to do this. See your device manufacturer’s instructions for further details.

**What We Do With The Information We Collect**

We use the information that we collect for the following purposes:

  * For the purposes for which you provided it;
  * To send you information about your relationship or transactions with us;
  * To send you alerts or other communications;
  * To notify you about new features of the Whiskey Riff  Services, special events, or products, services, and special offers;
  * To administer sweepstakes and contests;
  * To process and respond to your inquiries;
  * To contact you with information that we believe will be of interest to you;
  * To attribute content that you make available through the Whiskey Riff  Services;
  * To generate and review reports and data about our user base and service usage patterns;
  * To analyze the accuracy, effectiveness, usability, or popularity of the Whiskey Riff  Services;
  * To improve the content and features of the Whiskey Riff  Services or develop new Whiskey Riff  Services;
  * To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you see on the Whiskey Riff  Services;
  * To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Whiskey Riff  Services; and
  * To administer and troubleshoot the Whiskey Riff Services.

The Whiskey Riff Services are supported by advertising revenue. We will send you commercial email on behalf of ourselves, our affiliates, and advertisers. Each such email we send you will have an opt-out that you can use to stop receiving such communications.

We may aggregate and/or anonymize information collected by the Whiskey Riff Services or via other means so that the information does not identify you. Our use and disclosure of aggregated, anonymized, and other non-personal information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may disclose it to others without limitation for any purpose.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We will make your information available to other companies, websites, applications or people in the circumstances described below:

  * We may rent, sell, or share your information with non-affiliated third parties: (a) in order to provide services or products that you have requested; (b) when we have your permission; or (c) as described in this Privacy Policy.
  * We may share your information with any affiliate or agent of Whiskey Riff in order to provide the Whiskey Riff Services or advertising or to communicate with you on our behalf.
  * When you sign up to participate in a contest or sweepstakes, your information may also be provided to our sweepstakes or contest advertisers, operators, or sponsors and the use of that information will be also governed by those advertisers’, operators’, or sponsors’ privacy policies or practices.
  * We may disclose your information in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process we receive, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims.
  * We may share your information with third-party advertisers and advertising networks or others with which we have a contractual relationship in aggregated or non-personally identifiable forms. Except when such business partners are acting on our behalf or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will obtain your consent before we share your email address, phone number or street address with them so that they may send you promotional information about their products and services directly.
  * We may disclose your information when we believe it appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety or property of any person, violations of the Terms of Use for the Whiskey Riff Services, and/or to protect our rights and property.

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets.  Your information may also be transferred to a trustee or other person in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy or other insolvency event.

**How You Can Access and Update Your Information**

You may review and update certain user profile information by logging in to the relevant portions of the Whiskey Riff Services where such information may be updated (if available) or by contacting us at  **wes [at] whiskeyriff [dot] com**

**How We Protect Information**

We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the unauthorized access, destruction or alteration of your information. Despite our best efforts, however, no security measures are completely impenetrable.

**Linked Sites and Advertisements**

The Whiskey Riff Services may contain links to third-party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those third-party websites.

We have relationships with third-party providers to provide content, products, services, and functionality through the Whiskey Riff Services. When you visit sites or use any Whiskey Riff Services provided in conjunction with one or more of these third-party providers and the brands of those providers appear on the site or Whiskey Riff Services in connection with such content, products, services, or functionality, we may share any information you provide or that is collected during your use of those Whiskey Riff Services with those providers. In some cases, the provider may collect information from you directly, in which case the provider’s privacy policy (which may differ from this Privacy Policy) would apply. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of any of our providers, you should contact the provider directly for more information.

**Users from Outside the United States**

The Whiskey Riff Services are hosted in the United States and are governed by United States law. If you are using the Whiskey Riff Services from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our databases are operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Whiskey Riff Services, you consent to your information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in our Privacy Policy.

**Children**

Whiskey Riff prohibits registration or subscription by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please send an email to  **wes [at] whiskeyriff [dot] com**

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of personal information disclosed to those parties.

**No Rights of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.

**Policy Updates**

Whiskey Riff reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Whiskey Riff Services following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here and notify you by email or by means of a notice on our website before such changes take effect. If the material changes concern practices where we have represented that we will obtain your consent to use or disclose your personally identifiable information, we will obtain your consent before taking any action inconsistent with those representations.

**Copyright Policy**

These Copyright Policy cover all of the websites and any associated content, including without limitation, any and all mobile or desktop applications, Apps, email, over-the-top-platforms, streaming services, software, services, RSS and Mobile Services (as defined below) or other materials or services made available on, from, or through websites (collectively, the “Websites”) of Momentum Media, LLC and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Momentum Media”). All media on the Websites are either: licensed by Momentum Media, submitted to the Websites by users, readily available and believed to be in the public domain, or used in “fair use” under the U.S. Copyright Act.  Momentum Media respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects its users to do the same.

**For Copyright Owners.**

If you are a copyright owner of a photograph, video, or other material that appears on any of the Websites, which you claim violates your copyright, please notify us as provided below.  If you are unsure whether the content you are reporting is infringing your legal rights, you may wish to seek legal guidance.  Keep in mind that submitting intentionally misleading reports of infringement may be punishable under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. Section 512 (“DMCA”) in the United States or similar laws in other countries.

**Notification of Copyright Infringement – DMCA**

Momentum Media is an Online Service Provider under the DMCA.  Momentum Media respects the legitimate rights of copyright owners and has adopted an efficient notice and takedown procedure as required by the DMCA and described herein.  This policy is intended to guide copyright owners in utilizing that procedure, and also to guide users and webmasters in restoring access to websites or content that is disabled due to a mistake.

**Delivery of the Notice**

Deliver all takedown Notices as provided by this Copyright Policy to Momentum Media by Email as follows:

BY EMAIL TO:  wes[at]whiskeyriff.com

Upon receipt of a valid Notice, Momentum Media will process the claim, which may result in removing or disabling access to the allegedly infringing material, subject to the user’s or webmaster’s right to submit a Counter-Notification claiming lawful use of the disabled works. In appropriate circumstances, Momentum Media will have the disputed material removed from public view, and will also notify the user or webmaster who posted the allegedly infringing material, which notification may include a complete copy of the Notice submitted regarding that material.

**Notice to Owners of Copyrighted Works**

If you are a copyright owner, authorized to act on behalf of one, or authorized to act under any exclusive right under copyright, please report alleged copyright infringements taking place on or through the Website by completing the following DMCA notice (“Notice”) and delivering it to Website’s Designated Copyright Agent, either in writing or by email, as provided for herein.

As a copyright owner, to provide Momentum Media with a proper valid Notice your copyright claim, your notice must be in English and must substantially contain the following:

i. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;

ii. An identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single Notice, a representative list of such works at that site;

iii. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material. This identification should include information reasonably sufficient to permit Momentum Media to locate the material, such as any URLs identifying the allegedly infringing material along with any other information that might assist Momentum Media’s Designated Copyright Agent in investigating your claim;

iv. Information reasonably sufficient to permit Momentum Media to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the you may be contacted;

v. A statement that the you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by you, your agent, or the law; and

vi. A statement that the information in the Notice is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Failure to include all of the above information may result in a delay in processing the DMCA Notification.  If you materially misrepresent that any material infringes your copyright interest, you may be liable for damages, including court costs and attorneys’ fees, and could be subject to criminal prosecution for perjury.

**Material Originating From Another Website**

If the allegedly infringing material originates from another website and you believe that this Website has cached that material, then confirm any of the following that apply:

i. The material has been removed from the originating site or access to the material on the originating site has been disabled;

ii. A court has ordered that the material be removed from the originating site; and/or

iii. A court has ordered that access to the material on the originating site be disabled.

Failure to include all of the above information may result in a delay in processing the DMCA Notification.  If you materially misrepresent that any material infringes your copyright interest, you may be liable for damages, including court costs and attorneys’ fees, and could be subject to criminal prosecution for perjury.

**Counter-Notifications**

If you receive notice that material that you submitted has been removed by Momentum Media pursuant to a Notice, and you believe that removal was in error or not pursuant to a valid copyright claim, you may seek to have the material replaced by submitting a Counter-Notice to Momentum Media.

Counter-Notifications must be submitted by the original uploader or an agent authorized to act on their behalf, such as an attorney.  After Momentum Media receives your Counter-Notification, it will forward the Counter-Notification to the party who submitted the original claim of copyright infringement.  Please note that when Momentum Media forwards the notice, it will include your personal information.  By submitting a counter notification, you consent to having your information revealed in this way. Momentum Media will not forward the counter notification to any party other than the original claimant.

To be effective and valid, Counter-Notices must contain substantially the following:

i. A physical or electronic signature of the subscriber;

ii. Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access to it was disabled;

iii. A statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled; and

iv. Your name, address, and telephone number, and a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the judicial district in which the address is located, or if your address is outside of the United States, for any judicial district in which Momentum Media may be found, and that you will accept service of process from the uploader of the infringing material or an agent of such person.
